<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<assignment xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imscc_extensions/assignment" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imscc_extensions/assignment http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/cc_extensions/cc_extresource_assignmentv1p0_v1p0.xsd" identifier="ib5d0c82d-9dee-468c-ba2c-9f77dbff1c4f">
  <title>Types of Evidence and Fingerprint Analysis Assignment</title>
  <instructor_text texttype="text/html">&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img src="Content/shutterstock_169636037.jpg" width="400" height="600"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a crime has occurred, criminal investigators use scientific techniques and/or forensic science experts to help identify and interpret any physical evidence from the crime scene. Physical evidence from a crime scene comes in many different forms, such as fingerprints, hair, blood, saliva, semen, skin, bone, bullets, bullet casings, paint fragments, and fibres.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #008000; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Individualized Physical Evidence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is unique and can be directly linked to a specific person and/or source. Ex. fingerprints, DNA, bullets, dental impressions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #008000;"&gt;Identified Physical Evidence&lt;/span&gt; shares a common source; it can be grouped into a class of items having similar properties. Ex. clothing, shoe prints, blood type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complete the following assignment about crime scene procedures.&amp;nbsp; Click on the image below to make a copy of the Types of Evidence Assignment.&amp;nbsp; Remember to double click the top of the document to open the header and add your name to the document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1h0Xr2WaWh5ziLGMGPoKaktSMLkTI1cs9xZlgpM8MGFk/copy" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="/content/enforced/37038-20-21_Q4_ForensicStudies25_Per4(A)_Sec/Content/Forensics%20Assignment%20(1).png" alt="types of evidence assignment" width="200" height="226" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_text-bottom"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 style="text-align: left;"&gt;When you have done this, submit your assignment below by uploading your file and clicking the Submit button.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;If you need a refresher on how to submit your assignments, you can access the steps in the Course Information section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</instructor_text>
  <submission_formats>
    <format type="file" />
  </submission_formats>
  <gradable points_possible="20.000000000">true</gradable>
</assignment>